19th-20th Century North American Architecture Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- United States (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 15)
    - San Francisco, CA (Box 131)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 133)
        - Roos House (Box 133)
        - Sansome House (Box 133)
        - Taylor House (Box 133)
      - Housing (Box 133)
      - Industrial Buildings (Box 133)
      - Office Buildings (Box 133)
        - Goldberg-Bowen Building (Box 133)
        - Hallidie Building (Box 133)
        - Red Cross Building (Box 133)
      - Prisons (Box 133)
      - Schools (Box 133)
      - Stores (Box 133)
        - Gift Shop (Box 133)
    - San Gabriel, CA (Box 133)
    - San Idelfonso, NM (Box 133)
    - San Juan Bautista, CA (Box 133)
    - San Juan Capistrano, CA (Box 133)
    - San Luis Rey de Francia, CA (Box 133)
    - San Mateo, CA (Box 133)
    - San Miguel, CA (Box 133)
    - San Pedro, CA (Box 133)
      - Various (Box 133)
      - Housing (Box 133)
    - San Pedro Martir, CA (Box 133)
    - Santa Barbara, CA (Box 134)
      - Various (Box 134)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 134)
        - Bingham House (Box 134)
        - Gavit House (Box 134)
        - Lidley House (Box 134)
        - Ludington House (Box 134)
        - Slater House (Box 134)
        - Slavin House (Box 134)
    - Santa Cruz Mounts, CA (Box 134)
    - Santa Fe, NM (Box 134)
      - Various (Box 134)
      - Museums (Box 134)
    - Santa Ines, CA (Box 134)
    - Santa Monica, CA (Box 134)
      - Houses-Apartments (Box 134)
        - Shangri House, LA (Box 134)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 134)
        - Eames House (Box 134)
        - Entenza House (Box 134)
      - Industrial Building (Box 134)
    - Santo Domingo, NM (Box 134)
    - Sarasota, FL (Box 134)
      - Houses (Box 134)
        - Deeds House (Box 134)
        - Harkavy House (Box 134)
        - Healy House (Box 134)
        - Twitchell House (Box 134)
        - Kate Wheelan House (Box 134)
      - Schools (Box 134)
        - High School I (Riverview) (Box 134–135)
        - High School II (Box 135)
    - Saratoga Springs, NY (Box 135)
      - General (Box 135)
      - Hotels (Box 135)
        - Various (Box 135)
        - United States Hotel (Box 135)
      - Houses (Box 135)
    - Saugus, MA (Box 135)
    - Sausalito, CA (Box 135)
    - Savannah, GA (Box 135)
      - Banks (Box 135)
      - Churches (Box 135)
        - Various (Box 135)
        - Cathedral of S. John (Box 135)
        - Christ Church (Box 135)
      - Government Buildings (Box 135)
      - Houses (Box 135)
        - Bullock House (Box 135)
        - Green House (Box 135)
        - Hermitage House (Box 135)
        - McAlpine House (Box 135)
    - Savin Rock, CT (Box 135)
    - Scarsborough, NY (Box 135)
    - Scarsdale, NY (Box 135)
    - Schenectady, NY (Box 135)
      - Various (Box 135)
      - Schools (Box 135)
        - Union College (Box 135)
    - Sea Bright, NJ (Box 135)
      - Houses (Box 135)
    - Sea Cliff, L.I., NY (Box 135)
    - Seal Harbor, ME (Box 135)
    - Seattle, WA (Box 135)
      - Various (Box 135)
      - Churches (Box 136)
      - Museums (Box 136)
    - Sedona, AZ (Box 136)
    - Sewaren, NJ (Box 136)
    - Shafter, CA (Box 136)
    - Shawneetown, IL (Box 136)
    - Sherman, WY (Box 136)
    - Shoemaker, CA (Box 136)
    - Short Hills, NJ (Box 136)
      - Houses (Box 136)
    - Sidney, OH (Box 136)
    - Sierra Madre, CA (Box 136)
    - Siesta Key, FL (Box 136)
    - Silverado, CA (Box 136)
    - Silver Lake, OH (Box 136)
    - Simsbury, CT (Box 136)
      - Planning (Box 136)
      - Churches (Box 136)
    - Sioux City, IA (Box 136)
      - Government Building (Box 136)
        - Court House (Box 136)
    - Smithfield, VA (Box 136)
    - Solon, OH (Box 136)
    - Somes Sound, ME (Box 136)
    - Southampton, NY (Box 136)
      - Houses (Box 136)
        - Breese House (Box 136)
        - Ford House (Box 136)
        - Rogers House (Box 137)
    - South Bend, IN (Box 137)
    - South Carolina, State of (Box 137)
      - Berkeley County (Box 137)
        - Mulberry Castle (Box 137)
      - Charleston, County (Box 137)
        - Pompion Hill Chapel (Box 137)
        - S. Andrew's Church (Box 137)
      - Georgetown County (Box 137)
    - South Coventry, CT (Box 137)
      - Various (Box 137)
      - Nathan Hale Homestead (Box 137)
    - Southern Pines, NC (Box 137)
    - South Framingham, MA (Box 137)
    - South Norwalk, CT (Box 137)
    - Southport, L.I., NY (Box 137)
    - South Sudbury, MA (Box 137)
    - Springfield, IL (Box 137)
      - Government Buildings (Box 137)
      - Houses (Box 137)
    - Springfield, MA (Box 137)
      - Churches (Box 137)
      - Government Buildings (Box 137)
      - Museums (Box 137)
    - Springfield, SC (Box 137)
    - Spring Glen, CT (Box 137)
    - Spring Green, WI (Box 137)
      - Houses (Box 137)
        - Misses Lloyd Jones House (Box 137)
        - Taliesin III (Box 138)
          - Exterior (Box 138)
          - Interior (Box 138)
      - Schools (Box 138)
    - Stamford, CT (Box 138)
    - Stanford, CA (Box 138)
    - Staten Island, NY (Box 138)
    - Stateburg, SC (Box 138)
    - Staunton Hill, VA (Box 138)
    - Stockbridge, MA (Box 138)
    - Stonington, CT (Box 138)
    - Stockton, CA (Box 138)
    - Stowe, VT (Box 138)
    - Stratford, CT (Box 138)
    - Sumter, SC (Box 138)
    - Sun City, AZ (Box 138)
    - Sunbury, CA (Box 138)
    - Sunnyvale, CA (Box 138)
    - Sussex, VA (Box 138)
    - Swampscott, MA (Box 138)
    - Swathmore, PA (Box 139)
    - Syracuse, NY (Box 139)
    - Tabira, NM (Box 139)
    - Tabor, PA (Box 139)
    - Talbot County, MD (Box 139)
      Xx Wye House
    - Taliesin East (Box 139)
      Xx Spring Green, WI
    - Tampa, FL (Box 139)
    - Tarrytown, NY (Box 139)
    - Taunton, MA (Box 139)
    - Templeton, MA (Box 139)
    - Thomaston, ME (Box 139)
    - Thousand Island Park, NY (Box 139)
    - Toledo, OH (Box 139)
      - Planning (Box 139)
      - Museums (Box 139)
    - Tombstone, AZ (Box 139)
    - Topeka, KS (Box 139)
      - Banks (Box 139)
    - Topsfield, MA (Box 139)
      - Capen House (Box 139)
    - Torresdale, PA (Box 139)
    - Trampas, NM (Box 139)
    - Treasure Island, FL (Box 140)
    - Trento, NJ (Box 140)
      - Bath House (Box 140)
      - Jewish Community Center (Box 140)
      - Trent House (Box 140)
    - Troy, NY (Box 140)
    - Trumbull, CT (Box 140)
    - Tuckahoe, NY (Box 140)
    - Tucson, AZ (Box 140)
      - Housing (Box 140)
    - Tulsa, OK (Box 140)
      - Churches (Box 140)
        - Church of the Christ King (Box 140)
        - Boston Avenue Church (Box 140)
      - Houses (Box 140)
      - Stores (Box 140)
    - Tuscaloosa, AL (Box 140)
    - Tuskegee, AL (Box 140)
    - Tuxedo Park, NY (Box 140)
      - Houses (Box 140)
        - Various (Box 140)
        - Chandler Cottage (Box 140)
        - Kent House (Box 140)
        - Loomis House (Box 140–141)
        - Lorillard House (Box 141)
    - Tyrone, NM (Box 141)
    - Umatilla, FL (Box 141)
    - Urbana, IL (Box 141)
    - Utica, NY (Box 141)
      - Banks (Box 141)
      - Government Buildings (Box 141)
      - Houses (Box 141)
        - Various (Box 141)
        - Fountain Elms (Box 141)
      - Museums (Box 141)
        - Munson William Proctor Museum (Box 141)
    - Vancouver, WA (Box 141)
    - Vandergrift, PA (Box 141)
    - Venice, CA (Box 141)
    - Venice, FL (Box 141)
    - Vernon, CT (Box 141)
    - Villa Nove, PA (Box 141)
    - Vina, CA (Box 141)
    - Virginia, State of (Box 141)
      - Various (Box 141)
      - Charles City County (Box 141)
        - Shirley (Box 141)
        - Westover (Box 141)
          - Exterior (Box 141)
          - Interior (Box 141)
      - Fairfax County (Box 141)
        - Guston Hall (Box 142)
          - Exterior (Box 142)
          - Interior (Box 142)
        - Pohick Church (Box 142)
        - Mount Vernon (Box 142)
          - Exterior (Box 142)
          - Interior (Box 142)
      - Fluvanna County (Box 142)
        - Bremo (Box 142)
      - Gloucerster County (Box 142)
        - Rosewell (Box 142)
      - Goochland County (Box 142)
      - Halifax County (Box 142)
        - Berry Hill (Box 142)
      - James City County (Box 142)
        - Carter's Grove (Box 142)
          - Exterior (Box 142)
          - Interiors (Box 142–143)
      - King George County (Box 143)
        - Marmion (Box 143)
      - Lancaster County (Box 143)
        - Christ Church (Box 143)
      - New Kent County (Box 143)
      - Powhatan County (Box 143)
      - Prince George County (Box 143)
        - Brandon (Box 143)
      - Princess Anne County (Box 143)
        Xx Adam Throughgood see Norfolk, VA
      - Richmond County (Box 143)
        - Mount Airy (Box 143)
        - Sabine Hall (Box 143)
      - Stafford County (Box 143)
        - Aquia Creek Church (Box 143)
      - Surrey County (Box 143)
        - Bacon's Castle (Box 143)
      - Westmoreland County (Box 143)
        - Stratford Hall (Box 143)
          - Exterior (Box 143)
          - Interior (Box 143)
    - Virginia City, NV (Box 143)
    - Waban, MA (Box 143)
    - Wallingford, CT (Box 143)
    - Walnut Hills, OH (Box 144)
    - Waltham, MA (Box 144)
      - Houses (Box 144)
        - Christopher Gore House (Box 144)
        - Lyman House (Box 144)
      - Schools (Box 144)
    - Warren, NJ (Box 144)
    - Washington, D.C. (Box 144)
      - General (Box 144)
      - General Plans (Box 144)
      - General Planning (Box 144)
        - Senate Park Commission Plan 1901 (Box 144)
        - Triangle Development Project (Box 144)
      - General Views (Box 144)
      - Airports (Box 144)
        - National Airport (Box 144)
        - Dulles International Airport (Box 144)
      - Churches (Box 144)
        - Washington National Cathedral (Box 144)
        - Sacred Heart Church (Box 145)
        - Unitarian Church (Box 145)
      - Garages (Box 145)
        - Star Parking Garage (Box 145)
      - Government Buildings (Box 145)
        - Various (Box 145)
        - Capitol Building (Box 145)
          - Designs and Plans (miscellaneous) (Box 145)
          - Bullfinch Design (Box 145)
          - Latrobe Design (Box 145)
          - Thornton Design (Box 145)
          - Early views (Box 145)
          - Exterior (Box 145)
            - Various (Box 145)
            - Dome (Box 145)
            - House of Representatives (Box 145)
            - Senate (Box 145)
              - Exterior (Box 145)
              - Interior (Box 145)
            - Interior (Box 145)
              - Various (Box 145)
              - Main Rotunda (Box 145)
              - Marble Room (Box 145)
              - Statuary Hall (Box 145)
          - Commerce Department Building (Box 145)
          - Court House (Box 145)
          - Federal Reserve Building (Box 145)
          - General Accounting Office (Box 145)
          - Internal Revenue Building (Box 145)
          - Federal Reserve (Box 146)
          - Pan American Building (Box 146)
          - Patent Office (Box 146)
          - Pentagon (Box 146)
            Xx Arlington, VA
          - Senate Office Building (Box 146)
          - State Department Building (Box 146)
          - Supreme Court Building (Box 146)
          - Treasury Department Building (Box 146)
          - War and Navy Building (Box 146)
          - White House (Box 146)
          - Exterior (Box 146)
          - Interior (Box 146)
            - Blue Room (Box 146)
            - East Room (Box 146)
            - Green Room (Box 146)
            - Lobby (Box 146)
            - State Dinning Room (Box 146)
      - Hotels (Box 146)
        - Statler Hotel (Box 146)
        - Willard House (Box 146)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 146)
        - Henry Adams (Box 146)
        - Dumbarton House (Box 146)
        - Octagon House (Box 146)
        - Tudor Place (Box 146)
        - Warder House (Box 146)
      - Libraries (Box 146)
        - Folger Shakespeare Library (Box 146–147)
        - Library of Congress (Box 147)
        - Public Library (Box 147)
      - Monuments (Box 147)
        - Jefferson Memorial (Box 147)
        - Lincoln Memorial (Box 147)
        - Washington Monument (Box 147)
      - Museums (Box 147)
        - Corcoran Gallery (Box 147)
        - Freer Art Gallery (Box 147)
        - National Gallery of Art (Box 147)
        - Smithsonian Institute (Box 147)
      - Office Buildings (Box 147)
        - Carnegie Institute (Box 147)
        - D.A.R. Building (Box 148)
        - Longfellow Building (Box 148)
        - Red Cross Building (Box 148)
      - Schools (Box 148)
        - Academy of Sciences (Box 148)
        - Academy of Sciences (Box 148)
      - Stations (Box 148)
        - Baltimore & Potomac Station (Box 148)
        - Union Station (Box 148)
        - Baltimore & Washington Station (Box 148)
      - Stores (Box 148)
        - Hecht Co. (Box 148)
      - Theaters (Box 148)
    - Waterbury, CT (Box 148)
      - General (Box 148)
      - Hospital (Box 148)
    - Water Mill, RI (Box 148)
    - Waukegan, IL (Box 148)
      - Hospital (Box 148)
    - Waukesha, WI (Box 148)
    - Wausau, WI (Box 148)
    - Wayzata, MN (Box 148)
    - Wellesley, MA (Box 148)
    - Westborough, MA (Box 148)
    - Westbury, NY (Box 148)
    - Westchester, NY (Box 148)
    - Westchester, PA (Box 148)
    - West Hartford, CT (Box 149)
    - West Haven, CT (Box 149)
    - Westerly, RI (Box 149)
    - Westfield, MA (Box 149)
    - West Lafayette, IN (Box 149)
    - West Medford, MA (Box 149)
    - West Newton, MA (Box 149)
    - West Orange, NJ (Box 149)
      Xx Lewellyn Park
    - WestPoint, NY (Box 149)
      - Schools (Box 149)
    - Westmoreland, NH (Box 149)
    - Westport, CT (Box 149)
    - West Warwick, RI (Box 149)
    - Wethersfield, CT (Box 149)
      - Houses (Box 149)
        - Butlaph-Williams House (Box 149)
        - Joseph Webb House (Box 149)
    - Wheatley Hills, L.I., NY (Box 149)
    - Wheeler, TN (Box 149)
    - Whitehall, SC (Box 149)
    - Whitemarsh, PA (Box 149)
      - Houses (Box 149)
        - Squares Shadows (Box 149)
    - White Plans, NY (Box 149)
    - Whitneyville, CT (Box 150)
    - Wickford, RI (Box 150)
    - Wilkes-Barre, PA (Box 150)
    - Williamsburg, VA (Box 150)
      - Various (Box 150)
      - Bruton Church (Box 150)
      - Capitol (Box 150)
      - Governor's Palace (Box 150)
      - Raleigh Tavern (Box 150)
      - Jail (Box 150)
      - Court House (Box 150)
      - William and Mary College (Box 150)
      - Pillory (Box 150)
      - Houses (Box 150)
        - Brush-Everard House (Box 150)
        - James Galt Cottage (Box 150)
        - Ludwell Paradise House (Box 150)
        - George Wythe House (Box 150)
        - The Magazine House (Box 150)
      - Stores (Box 150)
        - Apothecary Shop (Box 150)
        - Cabinet Market Shop (Box 150)
        - Smithy of Elkanah Deane (Box 150)
    - WilliamsPort, PA (Box 150)
    - Williamstown, MA (Box 151)
      - Houses (Box 151)
        - Robinson House (Box 151)
    - Willimantic, CT (Box 151)
    - Willow Run, MI (Box 151)
    - Willmette, IL (Box 151)
    - Wilmington, DE (Box 151)
    - Wilminston, NC (Box 151)
    - Widham, CT (Box 151)
    - Windsor, CT (Box 151)
    - Windsor Locks, CT (Box 151)
    - Winnetka, IL (Box 151)
      - Houses (Box 151)
      - Schools (Box 151)
    - Winona, MN (Box 151)
    - Winston Salem, NC (Box 152)
    - Winterthur Museum (Box 152)
      Xx U.S General
    - Wiscasset, ME (Box 152)
    - Woburn, MA (Box 152)
    - Woburn, MA (Box 152)
    - Woodbury, CT (Box 152)
    - Woodbury, L.I, NY (Box 152)
    - Wood's Hole, MA (Box 152)
    - Worcester, MA (Box 152)
      - Various (Box 152)
      - Churches (Box 152)
      - Government Buildings (Box 152)
      - Hospitals (Box 152)
      - Houses (Box 152)
      - Museums (Box 152)
      - Stations (Box 152)
    - Wright Field (Box 152)
    - Wyoming, NJ (Box 152)
    - Wyverwood, CA (Box 152)
    - Yamhill,OR (Box 152)
    - Yellow Springs, OH (Box 152)
    - Yonkers, NY (Box 153)
    - York, ME (Box 153)
    - York Harbor, ME (Box 153)
    - Yorktown, VA (Box 153)
    - Yorktown Heights, NY (Box 153)
    - Ypsilanti, MI (Box 153)
      Xx Willow Run Housing, see Architecture U.S. Willow Run
    - Yuba City, CA (Box 153)
    - Zia, NM (Box 153)
- Canada (Box 153)
  - Halifax, Nova Scotia (Box 153)
  - Kapuskasing (Box 153)
  - Montreal (Box 153)
    - Various (Box 153)
    - Stations (Box 153)
    - Squares (Box 153)
  - Oakville (Box 153)
  - Ottawa (Box 153)
  - Quebec (Box 153)
  - S. Catherine's (Box 153)
  - S. Stephen (Box 153)
  - Toronto (Box 153)
  - Victorias (Box 153)